{
    "id": "21d5780f57304f31ab7859c80aae4ff7",
    "title": "Present and past participle worksheet",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "0a9b97053f80420abdb519091ed46732",
            "title": "Present and Past Participle Worksheet",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "His ………………… coat needs mending.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "tattered",
                        "tattering"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "A ………………. stone gathers no moss.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "rolling",
                        "rolled"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "A ……………….. opportunity never returns.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "losing",
                        "lost"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He kept me ………………..",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "waiting",
                        "waited"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She looked ………………….",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "worried",
                        "worrying"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I saw the storm ………………….",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "approaching",
                        "approached"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………… a noise, I turned around.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Hearing",
                        "Heard"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Being ………………….., he quit his job.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "dissatisfied",
                        "dissatisfying"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Being ………………… with work, I couldn’t meet them.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "occupied",
                        "occupying"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………….. by his wife, he persevered.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Encouraged",
                        "Encouraging"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}